Ostania's capital, Berlint.
This old woman is a liaison for
Westalis' intelligence, WISE.
The man's name is Loid Forger.
Also known by his code name, Twilight.
He is a spy.
It seems that a new mission
has been assigned
alongside the important one
that is ongoing.
I've done this for over ten years.
The same old daily life.
Peace is only temporary.
I wonder if there will come a time when
we're not needed anymore.
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
Mission accomplished.
Hello, or shall I say good evening,
Twilight.
Good work with
completing your mission so quickly.
How is Operation Strix progressing?
The paramount task
he was discreetly assigned
to protect the peace
of the East and West was…
It's going well. I was able to
get a wife and child as well.
The mission is to form a local family
and infiltrate a certain school
in order to uncover
the war plans of the enemy.
Understood.
The iron rule of being a spy
is to keep a low profile.
Keep playing the role of a normal family.
I know.
Have you quit smoking?
Well, I do have a child now.
That is how the Forger family came to be.
Loid said that he was going to be late,
so shall we go out for dinner?
Okay.
I guess doctors are quite busy.
It must be tough.
Father isn't really a doctor.
The daughter, Anya, who was taken in
by chance from an orphanage…
Father's job is being a spy!
Today, he went to
bring down an arms dealer.
…she is a telepath that can read minds.
I'm putting away my dishes!
Thank you, Anya!
It won't come off.
The wife, Yor, who married into the family
for mutual convenience…
I can still smell the blood
of the man I killed yesterday.
…she is a full-on assassin.
A spy, a telepath, and an assassin.
The three live together
while hiding their true identities
from each other for their own sake,
and their
not-so-normal family life continues.
There are a number of assignments
throughout the day
apart from Operation Strix.
The lack of employees in our organization
is becoming serious.
When I get home, my fake family awaits me.
There's not a day I can relax as an agent.
Don't you think there's something wrong
with the husband living across from us?
It's the weekend,
yet he's working so late again.
Are they our neighbors?
It's so sad that he doesn't spend time
with his young child!
I hardly see the three of them together.
He's probably out cheating on his wife!
How awful!
Or maybe he got fired from his job,
and he feels awkward coming home.
I was careless.
I was so busy with other duties
that I was neglecting my role
as the family man!
In a disguise operation,
even the slightest suspicion and distrust
from those around us, can be fatal.
I must do everything in my power
to restore the situation.
A danger to our family is
a danger to this world!
We're going out next weekend!
Where would you like to go,
just the three of us?
Anya, is that a penguin?
Okay! Shall we go to an aquarium?
Um… You look tired,
why don't you take it easy?
Yor. In order to
continue our fake marriage,
we must act like a normal family.
So, look forward to the weekend, okay?
I'm excited!
I'll have to finish
all my other missions by then.
Okay, shall we go?
Loid… Maybe you should rest.
It's no problem.
Oh, Mr. Forger.
How rare to see you
all together as a family!
The three of us
are headed to the aquarium.
How exciting, right, Anya?
Really…
To avoid any suspicion
that our family is fake,
we must appear to our neighbors that
we are a happy and normal family.
A father that takes us out to play
and a mother that's nice to my father,
are both very nice people.
Anya thinks her family is very normal.
It sounds very forced, but whatever.
Well, then. We'll be off.
Wait, nice and normal Father!
Another request for contact.
I have a bad feeling about this…
-I'm going to go buy a drink.
-Okay.
Agent Twilight.
We have another mission for you today.
I can't.
It's from WISE Headquarters--
I can't. Today's an important day
for Operation Strix.
Father! Hurry or else
the aquarium will crash down!
They just remodeled it so don't worry!
Wait a moment.
So that's that.
Um… One coffee and one juice--
Wait! Did she say aquarium?
Good work, Agent Twilight.
The mission is actually
at Berlint Aquarium.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
you were a step ahead of me.
No, that's not it. It's a coincidence.
Please just give me the coffee and juice.
Some information will be
exchanged at that aquarium!
Please give me my coffee and juice.
Listen, Twilight!
It's a method of creating a new type of
nuclear weapon from another country.
If this information falls into the hands
of terrorists, people in our country
will die in great numbers.
Fishes!
Octopus!
Starfish. A small shark!
She looks like she's having fun! Loid…
You're not looking so good. Are you okay?
I ended up taking on the mission…
But I've already shown my neighbors
that our family gets along just fine.
All I have to do is
finish this other mission…
Oh! It's Mr. Forger from across the hall!
What a coincidence!
-Hello!
-Wh… What!
We just arrived as well.
Now I can't let my guard down! No…
-I'll just get rid of them…
-Would you like to go around with us?
Yor!
What a good idea!
Father looks funny.
In order to seem normal,
we should spend time with our neighbors.
Oh, well.
I'll quickly finish my mission
and go back to weekend mode.
According to our information,
they smuggled a capsule containing a film
by having one of the penguins swallow it.
Why a penguin?
Two were brought in yesterday.
The recipient has not shown up yet.
Recover the item at all costs
before the enemy organization does!
Shall we go to the penguin corner?
Okay!
I love penguins! I want to see!
Welcome to the
biggest penguin park in the world!
P-P-P-Penguin!
This is our aquarium's top feature!
There are over 200 penguins!
Which penguin is the target?
There's no way I can check each one!
It'll be easier to just stop the terrorist
who'll come to get the film.
No… If I don't know when
the recipient will appear,
that'll be too difficult too.
It's impossible for me to
keep an eye on all the penguins by myself!
What shall I do? No…
There has to be a way!
There has to be markers they use
to discern the target!
Father is in a dilemma.
Loid is so focused.
He's like a child!
That fish looks delicious.
Where did my child go?
I hope she stops being angry with me…
Fish!
-It's hard to read the penguins' minds!
-Let's play!
I'm hungry!
Come over here!
Ugh! Ugh!
Father! That penguin doesn't look like
it's doing well!
It's drinking an awful lot of water
and spitting it out.
Maybe something is stuck in its throat…
It might be worth it to take a look.
Sorry, I'm going to go buy a drink.
Loid must be so tired and thirsty…
What happened to the newbie
who was supposed to come in today?
Late on the first day?
I'm sorry I'm late!
Young people these days.
I'll teach you how to feed them,
so follow me.
Okay!
In order to subtly get close to
the target penguin,
it was most efficient
to become a caretaker.
AGENT TWILIGHT SPECIAL SKILL: DISGUISE
The first thing a new employee needs to do
is to remember
the penguins' faces and names.
Did you read the roster thoroughly?
Yes, I took a look at it
in the waiting room earlier.
What do you mean "took a look at it"?
You idiot!
It takes time.
-Took me two years to memorize them all!
-Oh, Chief!
You're about to step on Petilda,
behind you!
She is, in fact, Petilda…
This one is Pemas
and this one is Pesca, right?
How do you know that, newbie?
Well their patterns, faces, and height
are all different.
Even I still make mistakes now…
What great observation skills and memory!
Fine. Now let's feed them. Come.
Where's the one I saw from outside…
That's him!
Pyarles, the Emperor Penguin!
I need to get to him right away…
I can't go forward!
Hungry ones and picky eaters.
They each have their own way of eating,
so watch closely.
I don't have time for that!
I have to get back
or they'll get suspicious!
Chief! Let me do it!
Huh?
I observed the veteran's movement
and realized…
What matters is how each penguin eats!
See who eats what and how much,
and the placement of each group!
As long as I figure that out…
Crowd control is a no-brainer!
We got a great newbie!
Huh? It looks like Pyarles
doesn't have an appetite.
He might be sick,
so I'll take him to the treatment room.
-Excuse us!
-Sure.
Sorry, buddy.
Bingo!
There's something stuck in his throat.
There's also a mark on
the bottom of his foot!
Give me one moment.
I'll take it out for you.
Hey, you.
What are you doing with that penguin?
He seems sick,
so I'm taking him to the treatment room.
I see. Then I'll take him.
I'm sorry. We have a rule that only
authorized personnel can touch them.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm a professor in the marine biology lab
at the University of Berlint
and I'm responsible for
managing the animals here.
This ID is fake. It's not made well.
Who are you--
I won't let you get away!
Stay still!
Hey, newbie!
Where are you going with that penguin?
The treatment room is that way!
I can't let the penguin go when I don't
know how many enemies are out there.
First priority is to secure the film.
I have to give up chasing after him.
Oh no… Where did Anya go?
I have to let the others outside know,
kill him,
and retrieve the film--
-What's with you?!
-Mother! I'm being kidnapped!
Anya!
Let go! What are you saying--
What are you doing…
to my child?!
Wow!
Are you all right?
Oh no. I went too far.
I hope he's not dead!
Wow.
This was how they successfully
recovered the film
and got information about the terrorist
organization from the people they caught.
Your husband is taking forever to return!
-I'm telling you, he's cheating on you!
-How awful!
That's not…
Sorry I was gone for so long!
Loid!
Ta-da!
A penguin!
What a big stuffed animal!
How did you get it?
It's a prize from the name guessing game
they were doing over there.
I really wanted to get it for Anya,
so I tried multiple times.
Oh, it was so hard!
Father's a liar. He got it with one try.
It's so cute
that he took the game so seriously.
I'm surprised. You're quite a good father!
I'm seeing you in a new light.
Not at all.
I'm just an ordinary father who is
running around trying to protect
his peaceful family life.
If I look closely, you're quite handsome.
I think I can manage to keep up
appearances here too.
But I'm fed up with overworking.
I'm going to complain to headquarters
and request a long vacation.
No… My duty is to maintain a world where
children don't cry and war doesn't occur.
I don't have time to stand still.
Father!
The dolphin show is about to start!
Sorry, can you walk slower?
Huh? You want me as Chief?! Why?!
I have nothing else to teach you.
I'm Director Kimera,
the head of the P2 secret organization.
You must be the newbie who just joined us.
My name is Penguin
and I came from the aquarium!
Nice to meet you!
Agent Anya.
-The item.
-Yes!
The tradition where
we both eat half of a peanut.
Once we do that, you'll officially be
a part of our organization.
Starting today,
you'll be Agent Penguin Man.
-Do your best to protect the peace.
-Yes, sir!
Agent Anya,
show the newbie around my hideout.
Okay-dokey!
This is the command center of the hideout!
We receive information every day
through this machine!
WATCHES ANIME
He's Agent Father.
He's a super elite that can do anything!
Is she playing "spy"?
She's Agent Mother.
She's strong but can't do anything else.
Am I that useless?!
They're both fine proteges of Anya.
Okay, next!
Anya loves that stuffed animal!
This is the bathroom!
You can heal your battle wounds here.
This is Anya's room.
I train here every day.
DOES HOMEWORK
And…
the top secret place of our organization.
Father's room and Mother's room!
Be careful.
If you find out the secrets of
these rooms, you won't leave here alive.
There might be very strong knives
and very strong bombs!
Well, then…
Hey! What are you doing?!
I told you so many times
you can't just go in!
Oh, no… It's just there's dangerous things
like scissors and heaters…
Actually, there are things that are
much more dangerous…
That's right. You can't go in!
I have poisonous needles in my room…
I hate both of you!
Anya's going to leave this house!
This isn't good. Operation Strix will
collapse at this pace!
What shall I do?!
Boss!
We don't have time for crying
if we have to maintain world peace!
Why don't we wrap up
the tour of the hideout
and head to our next mission.
That's right! Let's go get the bad guys!
Okay! Follow me you guys!
The candy store on Second Street
has been overrun by bad guys!
Let's go save them!
Huh?
Be careful.
There might be traps that
the enemy set up.
-You're so smart, Boss!
-What are they doing?
What a sweet family!
A spy has to keep a low profile…
Anya was treated to candy after that
and she cheered up,
so peace and calm was restored
in the Forger family.
MIXED NUTS
Subtitle translation by: Nana Onishi